Philip M. Sheppard Papers 1911-1976 1940-1976 Mss.Ms.Coll.65
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1946-1983; 28 boxes, 14 lin. feet
  - Remington, Charles L., 1953-61 (Box Series I-20)
  - Renwick, J. H., 1975-76 (Box Series I-20)
  - Republic of the Philippines. Bureau of Plant Industry, 1966 (Box Series I-20)
  - Republic of the Philippines. Bureau of Posts, 1966 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rewell, Raoul E., 1963 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rex, D. E., 1964 (Box Series I-20)
  - Reynolds, Margery M., n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Rhett, Beverly, [1956?] (Box Series I-20)
  - Richards, A. John, 1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Richardson, Barry John, 1969; 1972 (Box Series I-20)
  - Richardson, M. M. (Mrs. ), 1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Richter, N. C., 1955-56 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ricklefs, Robert E. (Box Series I-20)
    See Ser.I, Thomas Nelson & Sons
  - Riggio, S., 1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - Riley, P. A., 1964 (Box Series I-20)
  - Riley, Ralph, 1969 (Box Series I-20)
    See also Ser.I, Genetical Society
  - Rindge, Frederick H., 1953; 1956 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rivera, Maria Luisa, 1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rivers, Claude F., 1973-74 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rives, Max, 1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roberts, David F., 1958-59;1975-76 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roberts, S., n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Robertson, Alan, 1963; 1976; n.d. (Box Series I-20)
  - Robins, R. J., 1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Robinson, Ian, 1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Robinson, Roy, 1953; 1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roche, Patrick (Box Series I-20)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1953-69 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roderick, Gordon W., 1966-75 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rodriguez, Jose Ramon, 1974 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roff, Derek Anthony, 1972 (Box Series I-20)
    See also Ser.I, Butler, R.
  - Rogers, Stephen Clifford, 1975 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rogerson, Judith A., 1966-67 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roper, J. Alan, 1959-76 (Box Series I-20)
    See also Ser.I, Parsons, Peter A.
  - Rosenhead, Louis, 1958; 1965-67 (Box Series I-20)
  - Roseweir, John, 1964 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rothschild, Miriam, 1956-76; n.d. (Box Series I-20)
    Smith, David [A.S.]
  - Roudier, A., 1952 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rowe, F. P., 1962-65 (Box Series I-20)
  - Rowley, John, 1965 (Box Series I-20)
  - Royal Botanic Gardens, 1956 (Box Series I-20)
  - Royal College of Physicians, 1973-75 (Box Series I-20)
  - Royal Entomological Society of London, 1952-74 (Box Series I-20)
  - Royal Hotel (Box Series I-20)
  - The Royal Society (Box Series I-20)
    Leao, Aristides A.P.
    See also Ser.I, Brown, Keith
    See also Oversized
    - Folder #1, 1954-68 (Box Series I-20)
    - Folder #2, 1969-70 (Box Series I-20)
    - Folder #3, 1971-72 (Box Series I-21)
    - Folder #4, 1973 (Box Series I-21)
    - Folder #5, 1974-76 (Box Series I-21)
  - The Royal Society. Aldabra Research Committee (Box Series I-21)
    Lewontin, Richard C. (1969-70)
    -See also Ser.II, Royal Society.
    Aldabra Newsletter
    Aldabra Research Committee. Minutes
    - Folder #1, 1968-69 (Box Series I-21)
    - Folder #2, Jan.-Aug. 1970 (Box Series I-21)
    - Folder #3, Sep.-Oct. 1970 (Box Series I-21)
    - Folder #4, Nov.-Dec. 1970 (Box Series I-22)
    - Folder #5, 1971 (Box Series I-22)
    - Folder #6, 1972-73 (Box Series I-22)
  - Royal Society for the Promotion of Health, 1967 (Box Series I-22)
  - The Royal Society of Medicine, 1972 (Box Series I-22)
  - Rudd-Jones, D., 1975 (Box Series I-22)
  - Rudge, Michael R., 1969 (Box Series I-22)
    Stodddart, D.R.
  - Runcorn, S. K., 1958 (Box Series I-22)
  - Russell, William, 1971 (Box Series I-22)
  - Russell, [William] M. S., 1975 (Box Series I-22)
  - Ryman, B. E., 1973 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sacchi, C. F., 1951-52; 1960 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sage, B., 1965-68 (Box Series I-22)
  - St. Anne's College, Oxford, 1954 (Box Series I-22)
  - Salford University, Biology Society, 1973 (Box Series I-22)
  - Salkeld, P. N., 1969 (Box Series I-22)
  - Saluja, Patricia Gail, 1968 (Box Series I-22)
  - Salzano, F. M., 1971 (Box Series I-22)
  - Samino, [?], 1961 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sampford, Michael R., 1955;1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sanderson, Bridget, 1956-58 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sands, Margaret, 1976 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sanger, Ruth A., 1970; 1972 (Box Series I-22)
    See also Ser.I, Race, R.R.
  - Sargent, H. B., 1952 (Box Series I-22)
  - Satchell, J. E., 1956 (Box Series I-22)
  - Savage, Oswald, 1962 (Box Series I-22)
  - Savile, D. B. O., 1964 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sawicki, R. M., 1972 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sawyerr, Harry, 1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Saxton,G. A. N., 1971 (Box Series I-22)
  - Sbordoni, V., 1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Scali, Valerio, 1975-76 (Box Series I-22)
  - Scharloo, W., 1962 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schatz, A., 1976 (Box Series I-22)
  - Scheinberg, S. L., 1955 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schnetter, Martin, 1951 (Box Series I-22)
  - Schrager, G. R., 1966-74 (Box Series I-22)
    McConnell, R[ichard] B.
  - Science Press, 1954 (Box Series I-22)
  - Science Progress, 1965-69 (Box Series I-22)
    Lewis, Dan[iel]
  - Science Research Council (Box Series I-22)
    Seddon, John J.
    - Folder #1, 1964-66 (Box Series I-22)
    - Folder #2, 1967-68 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #3, 1969-70 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #4, 1971 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #5, 1972 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #6, 1973-74 (Box Series I-23)
    - Folder #7, 1975-76 (Box Series I-23)
  - Scossiroli, R. E., 1972-73 (Box Series I-24)
  - Scotch College, 1953 (Box Series I-24)
  - Scott, D. M., 1972 (Box Series I-24)
  - Scott, James, 1974; 1976 (Box Series I-24)
  - Scott, Richard, 1965 (Box Series I-24)
  - Scudamore, James M., 1966-70 (Box Series I-24)
    See also Ser.I, Dransfield, J.W.
  - Scudder, G. G. E., 1960; 1966 (Box Series I-24)
  - Searle, A. G., 1966 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sears, [?] (Mrs. ), 1975 (Box Series I-24)
  - Seddon, John J., 1966 (Box Series I-24)
    See also Ser.I, Science Research Council
  - Sedlack, J., 1961 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sells, Robert A., 1976 (Box Series I-24)
  - Semple, Andrew B., 1968-75 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sermonti, Giuseppe, 1972 (Box Series I-24)
  - Service, M. W., 1975 (Box Series I-24)
  - Seth, S. C., 1960 (Box Series I-24)
  - Shallcross, Lesley, 1973 (Box Series I-24)
  - Shaski, S. T., 1952 (Box Series I-24)
  - Shaw, [?] (Miss), 1964 (Box Series I-24)
  - Shaw, D. F., 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Shaw, Margaret, 1964 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sheehan, J., 1970 (Box Series I-24)
  - Shell International Petroleum Co., Ltd., 1961-66 (Box Series I-24)
  - Shepley, A. V., 1969 (Box Series I-24)
  - Shorrocks, Bryan, 1969 (Box Series I-24)
  - Shutt, Margaret S., 1975 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sibley, F. C., 1961 (Box Series I-24)
  - Siggs, L. W., 1975 (Box Series I-24)
  - Silber, Anne F., 1969 (Box Series I-24)
  - Silverman, [?], 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Simmonds, N. W., 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Simon Thomas, R. T., 1961 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sinden, R. E., 1965 (Box Series I-24)
  - Singer, Michael C., 1972-76 (Box Series I-24)
  - Siniscalco, M., 1954 (Box Series I-24)
  - The Sixty Club, 1973 (Box Series I-24)
  - Skipworth, Eric J., 1959; 1964 (Box Series I-24)
  - Slee, J., 1967 (Box Series I-24)
  - Small, P. Leonard, 1958; 1961; n.d. (Box Series I-24)
  - Smallman, F. Basil R., 1975 (Box Series I-24)
  - Smart, John, 1954 (Box Series I-24)
  - Smith, A. G., 1969 (Box Series I-24)
  - Smith, Audrey, 1971-72 (Box Series I-24)
  - Smith, Cedric A. B., 1955-75 (Box Series I-24)
    See also Ser.I, Lugg, J.W.H.
  - Smith, Clifford T., 1975; n.d. (Box Series I-24)
  - Smith, David A. S., 1972 (Box Series I-24)
    See also Ser.I, Rothschild, Miriam
  - Smith, J. D. D. (Box Series I-24)
    See Ser.I, Cain, Arthur J.
  - Smith, Kenneth M., 1953 (Box Series I-24)
  - Smith, Morfudd I., 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Smith, T. E., 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Smith-White, S., 1970; 1973 (Box Series I-24)
  - Smithells, Richard W., 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sobels, F. H., 1965 (Box Series I-24)
  - Societa Entomologica Italiana, 1952 (Box Series I-24)
  - Society of Opticians, 1974 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sokol, Robert R., 1954; 1957 (Box Series I-24)
  - Soliman, Hani, 1975-76 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sorman, Ann E., 1970 (Box Series I-24)
  - Southcott, R. V., 1967 (Box Series I-24)
  - Southern, H. N. (Mick), 1960; 1965 (Box Series I-24)
    See also Ser.I, Journal of Animal Ecology
  - Southwood, T. R. E., 1967-74 (Box Series I-24)
    See also Ser.I, Wright, J.W.
  - Spalding, D. Brian, 1972-76; n.d. (Box Series I-24)
  - Sparks, B., 1963 (Box Series I-24)
  - Spassky, B., 1954 (Box Series I-24)
  - Speakman, T., 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - The Spectator, 1964 (Box Series I-24)
  - Spencer, G. J., 1953 (Box Series I-24)
  - Speiss, E. B., 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Springfield Nurseries, Ltd., 1974 (Box Series I-24)
  - Spurway, Helen, 1953 (Box Series I-24)
  - Srivastava, A. S., 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Staddler, D. R., 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stalker, Harrison, 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Standfast, H. A., 1961 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stanton, W. R., 1956-57 (Box Series I-24)
  - Starmuhlner, Ferdinand, 1967 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stebbins, G. Ledyard, 1957; 1965-68; n.d. (Box Series I-24)
  - Steel, Robert W., 1960-73 (Box Series I-24)
    Thomas, Ivor
  - Steinberg, A. G., 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stenders, A., 1969 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stephens, C. E., 1967 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stern, C. (Curt), 1956; 1.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-24)
    Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Stern, K., 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stern, Kurt (Box Series I-24)
  - Sternberg, Hilgard O'Reilly, 1972-73 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stevenson, W. H., 1962 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stidston, S. T., 1952 (Box Series I-24)
  - Socker, B. A. D., 1960 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stoddart, D. R. (Box Series I-24)
    See Ser.I, Rudge, Michael R.
  - Stoller, B. B., 1976 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stone, Wilson S., 1955 (Box Series I-24)
  - Storace, Luciano, 1952 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stott, Dorothy, 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Street, H. E., 1968 (Box Series I-24)
  - Street, R., 1974 (Box Series I-24)
  - Strickland, [H. H. ?], 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stride, George, 1956 (Box Series I-24)
  - Stuart, [?] (Box Series I-24)
    See Ser.I, Gill, J.J.B.
  - Subak-Sharpe, John H. (Box Series I-24)
    See Ser.I, Genetical Society
  - Subden, Ronald E., 1972 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sumner, Colin, 1965-70 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sunderland, A. J., 1970 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sunderland, N., 1973 (Box Series I-24)
  - Suomalainen, Esko, 1973-74 (Box Series I-24)
    See also Ser.I, Turner, John (1966)
  - Sutherland, D., 1958 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sutcliffe, Judith N., 1974 (Box Series I-24)
  - Sutton, [?], 1957-58 (Box Series I-24)
  - Swansbury, G. John, 1974; 1976 (Box Series I-24)
  - Swets & Zeitlinger, 1957; 1960; n.d. (Box Series I-24)
  - Sylvestroni, E., 1954 (Box Series I-24)
  - Systematic Entomology, 1976 (Box Series I-24)
  - Szarski, Henryk, 1971 (Box Series I-24)
  - Szent-Ivany, J. J. H., 1961 (Box Series I-24)
  - Tambiah, M. S., 1965-66 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tanner, J., 1963 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tasker, M. C., 1968 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tate and Lyle Refineries Ltd., 1974 (Box Series I-25)
  - Taylor, C. J., 1953 (Box Series I-25)
  - Taylor, Ernest, 1973 (Box Series I-25)
  - Taylor, M. J., 1966 (Box Series I-25)
  - Taylor, St. C. S., 1973 (Box Series I-25)
  - Taylor, Sylvia, 1968 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tazima, Y., 1968 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thames and Hudson Ltd., 1967 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thatcher, T. O., 1954 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thoday, John M., 1953-75 (Box Series I-25)
    See also Ser.I, Heredity
  - Thomas, G., 1958 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thomas, Ivor, 1958 (Box Series I-25)
    See also Ser.I, Steel, Robert W.
  - Thomas, J. D., 1962; 1974 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thomas, K., 1969 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thomas, K. D., 1974 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thomas, Trevor C., 1970-72 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thomas, W[illiam] J., 1958 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thompson, J. D., 1968 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thompson, Linda, 1972 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thompson, Mary, 1964; n.d. (Box Series I-25)
  - Thomson, A. J., 1971 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thorn, Erik, 1956 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thornber, Cyril, 1963 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thorne, Fred, 1967-70 (Box Series I-25)
    Mori, J.R.
    See also Ser.I, Brower, Lincoln P.
  - Thornton, Ian W. B., 1964-67 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thornton, Marie, 1965-66 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thorpe, W. H., 1954 (Box Series I-25)
  - Thrift, H. J., 1972 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tilney-Bassett, R., 1967 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tinbergen, Nikolaas, 1962-76 (Box Series I-25)
    See also Ser.I, Davies, Clifford E.
    See also Ser.I, Vowles, David M.
  - Tinsley, T. W., 1956-57 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tipler, Terry, 1974 (Box Series I-25)
  - Todd, Pat (Box Series I-25)
  - Tomley, David, n.d. (Box Series I-25)
  - Tonn, Robert J., 1967-68 (Box Series I-25)
    Macdonald, W.W.
  - Townsend, Antony [G. H. ?], 1957 (Box Series I-25)
  - Treisman, Michel, 1963 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tremewan, W. Gerald, 1952 (Box Series I-25)
  - Trevor Crewe & Co., 1956 (Box Series I-25)
  - Trewavas, E., 1956-58 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tro[yman?], Tom, n.d. (Box Series I-25)
  - Turner, Angela, 1973 (Box Series I-25)
  - Tuner, G. H. (Mrs. Elsie E. ), 1963-73 (Box Series I-25)
  - Turner, John M., 1974-75 (Box Series I-25)
  - Turner, John R. G., 1959-1976; 15 folders (Box Series I-25)
    Brown, Keith S., Jr.
    Davies, D.R.
    Emsley, Mi[chael] G. (1963)
    Suomalainen., Esko (1966)
    See also Ser.I, Angseesing, Joseph P.A.,Folder #2
    See also Ser.I, Benson, Woodruff W.
    See also Ser.I, Brown,Keith
    Biographical and personal data; Clarke, Cyril Astley; Educational matters; Ford, Edmund Brisco; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Graduate study; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Population genetics; Publication; Recommendations; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Travel -- Surinam; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc. -- Fieldwork
    - Folder #1, 1959-1963 (Box Series I-25)
    - Folder #2, 1964 (Box Series I-25)
    - Folder #3, 1965 (Box Series I-25)
    - Folder #4, 1966 (Box Series I-25)
    - Folder #5, 1967-1968 (Box Series I-25)
    - Folder #6, 1970 (Box Series I-25)
    - Folder #7, 1971-1972 (Box Series I-25)
    - Folder #8, Jan.-Feb. 1973 (Box Series I-25)
    - Folder #9, Mar.-Dec. 1973 (Box Series I-26)
    - Folder #10, Jan.-Jun. 1974 (Box Series I-26)
    - Folder #11, Jul.-Dec. 1974 (Box Series I-26)
    - Folder #12, Jan.-Jun 1975 (Box Series I-26)
    - Folder #13, Jul.-Dec. 1975 (Box Series I-26)
    - Folder #14, Jan.-Jul. 1976 (Box Series I-26)
    - Folder #15, Aug.-Nov. 1976 (Box Series I-26)
  - Tweedie, M. C. Kenneth, 1964-69 (Box Series I-26)
  - Unamba, Josiah A., 1967-69 (Box Series I-26)
  - UNESCO (United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Org. ), 1967 (Box Series I-26)
  - Unidentified, 1949-76; n.d. (Box Series I-26)
  - Unigate Paediatric Workshops, 1976 (Box Series I-26)
  - U. S. Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare, 1959 (Box Series I-26)
  - The University Chest. Oxford, 1953-56 (Box Series I-26)
  - University Grants Committee, 1961-72 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of Adelaide, 1968 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of Birmingham (England), 1968 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of Bristol, 1975 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of California, Davis, 1968 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of Cambridge. Dept. of Genetics, 1969 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of Colorado. Institute of Arctic and Alpine Research, 1968 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of Liverpool (Box Series I-26)
    - Centre for Communication Studies, 1968 (Box Series I-26)
    - Department of Genetics, 1967-75; n.d. (Box Series I-26)
    - Department of Public Health, 1968-75 (Box Series I-26)
    - Department of Veterinary Pathology, n.d. (Box Series I-26)
    - Examinations Department, 1968 (Box Series I-26)
    - Faculty of Science. Dean., 1960; 1974 (Box Series I-26)
    - Finance Officer, 1960-74 (Box Series I-6)
    - Greenbank House Club, 1968 (Box Series I-26)
    - Guild of Undergraduates, 1969-76 (Box Series I-26)
    - Institute of Education. Science Teachers' Centre, 1969-70 (Box Series I-26)
    - Joint Committee on Legal Liability, 1974 (Box Series I-26)
    - Joint Committee on Research, 1965 (Box Series I-26)
    - Joint Matriculation Board, 1970 (Box Series I-26)
    - Librarian, 1967-68 (Box Series I-26)
    - Life Sciences Registration Sub-Committee, 1968 (Box Series I-26)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box Series I-26)
    - Pro-Vice Chancellor, 1969 (Box Series I-26)
    - Public Relations Office, 1968-69 (Box Series I-26)
    - Technical Panel, 1974 (Box Series I-26)
    - Vice Chancellor's Office, 1960 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of London, 1953 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of New England, 1967 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of Nottingham, 1970 (Box Series I-26)
  - University of Sheffield, 1956 (Box Series I-26)
  - University Registry, Oxford, 1956 (Box Series I-26)
  - Unrau, Ann E., 1967-68 (Box Series I-26)
  - Upton, Brooke M., 1969 (Box Series I-26)
  - Usher, George, 1956 (Box Series I-26)
  - Usher, Michael B., 1975 (Box Series I-26)
  - Vadilo, P. S., 1970 (Box Series I-27)
  - Valdeyron, G., 1974-75 (Box Series I-27)
  - Valentine, David H., 1968-73 (Box Series I-27)
  - Valletta, Anthony, 1957 (Box Series I-27)
  - Van Brink, Janny, 1960 (Box Series I-27)
  - Van-Dam, N., 1961 (Box Series I-27)
  - Van der Hammen, [?], 1975 (Box Series I-27)
  - Van der Veen, Ir. G., 1973 (Box Series I-27)
  - Van Emden, F., 1952 (Box Series I-27)
  - Vane-Wright, R. I., 1970; 1975 (Box Series I-27)
    See also Ser.I, Cain, Arthur J. (21 July, 1983)
  - Van Nostrand Co., 1967 (Box Series I-27)
  - Van Oss, R., 1956 (Box Series I-27)
  - Van Rood, J. J. (Box Series I-27)
  - Van Someren, V. G. L. (Victor Gurner Logan), 1956-1968; 2 folders (Box Series I-27)
    Clarke, Cyril Astley; Ford, Edmund Brisco; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Publication
    - Folder #1, 1956-1959 (Box Series I-27)
    - Folder #2, 1960-1968 (Box Series I-27)
  - Van Valen, Leigh, 1961-70 (Box Series I-27)
  - Van Sandt, Jane, 1974; n.d. (Box Series I-27)
  - Vanzolini, P. E. /, 1971-73 (Box Series I-27)
  - Varley, George C., 1973-75; n.d. (Box Series I-27)
  - Vepsalainen, Kurt, 1974 (Box Series I-27)
  - Vesco, J. P. (Box Series I-27)
  - Vickers Ltd., 1969 (Box Series I-27)
  - Vickery, Robert K., Jr., 1969-76 (Box Series I-27)
  - Vienjant, R., 1952 (Box Series I-27)
  - Vieu, R., 1956 (Box Series I-27)
    Griveaud, P.
  - Visoso, [Bert?], n.d. (Box Series I-27)
  - Vockeroth, J. Richard, 1953; 1957 (Box Series I-27)
  - Voipio, Paavo, 1954 (Box Series I-27)
  - Volpe, E. Peter, 1966 (Box Series I-27)
  - Von Ullmann, E. (Miss), 1953-59 (Box Series I-27)
  - Vosa, C. (Box Series I-27)
  - Vowles, David M., 1966 (Box Series I-27)
    Tinbergen, Niko[laas]
  - Waddington, C. H., 1961; 1973-75 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wagner, A. M. R., 1959 (Box Series I-27)
  - Walbank, F. W., 1975 (Box Series I-27)
  - Walker, B. A., 1973 (Box Series I-27)
  - Walker, S. M., 1966 (Box Series I-27)
  - Walker, Stanley, 1967-69; n.d. (Box Series I-27)
    See also Ser.I, Angseesing, Joseph
  - Wallace, Bruce, 1954-1963; 7.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-27)
    Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; Kettlewell, Henry Bernard Davis; Population genetics
  - Wallace, H., 1955 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wallace, Margaret E., 1968; 1972 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wallasey Golf Club, 1957 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wallis, J. (Mrs. ), 1975 (Box Series I-27)
  - Walsh, Brenda, 1967-69 (Box Series I-27)
  - Walsh, Niall P. (Box Series I-27)
  - Warburton, Frederick E., 1951 (Box Series I-27)
  - Ward, S. A., 1976 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wareing, P. F., 1957 (Box Series I-27)
  - Waring, Harry, 1965-69 (Box Series I-27)
  - Warren, Katherine Brehme, 1955; 1957 (Box Series I-27)
  - Warwick, N. G., 1973 (Box Series I-27)
  - Watanabe, Masato (Box Series I-27)
  - Waterhouse, Fred L., 1965 (Box Series I-27)
  - Watkin, Edward M., 1961 (Box Series I-27)
  - Watkins & Doncaster, 1957-58 (Box Series I-27)
  - Watson, Christabel (Lady), 1968 (Box Series I-27)
  - Watson, E. Janet, 1970-74 (Box Series I-27)
  - Watts-Russell, Penny, 1972 (Box Series I-27)
  - Weatherall, David J., 1968-75 (Box Series I-27)
  - Weber, Hermann, 1954; n.d. (Box Series I-27)
  - Weekend Telegraph, 1967 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wegner, A. M. R., 1960-61 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wehrmaker, A., 1955-56 (Box Series I-27)
  - Weidmann, Uli, 1960-1963 (Box Series I-27)
  - Weiner, J. S., 1962 (Box Series I-27)
  - Weir, Bruce S., 1970-72 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wells, M. J., 1959-60 (Box Series I-27)
  - Werrett, W. F., 1960 (Box Series I-27)
    Cole, R.K.
  - Wery, Alexandre, 1952 (Box Series I-27)
  - West, David A. (Box Series I-27)
    - Folder #1, 1959-64 (Box Series I-27)
    - Folder #2, 1964-76 (Box Series I-27)
  - Western Mail, 1965 (Box Series I-27)
  - Weston, M. E., 1956; n.d. (Box Series I-27)
  - Whalley, Paul E. S., 1957-58 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wharton, C. F. P., 1955-56 (Box Series I-27)
  - Whelan, R. F., 1972 (Box Series I-27)
  - Whitaker, R. J. (Box Series I-27)
    See Ser.I, Jones, J.W.
  - White, C., 1956 (Box Series I-27)
  - White, Edwin G., 1964-70 (Box Series I-27)
    See also Ser.I, Journal of Comparative Pathology and Therapeutics
  - White, G. A., 1957 (Box Series I-27)
  - White, Michael J. D., 1965-67 (Box Series I-27)
  - White, P. H. E., 1961; 1968 (Box Series I-27)
  - White, Richard J., 1976 (Box Series I-27)
  - Whitehead, Peter J., 1972 (Box Series I-27)
  - Whitehouse, H. L. K., 1966 (Box Series I-27)
  - Whittaker, J. A., 1968 (Box Series I-27)
  - Whitten, Maxwell John, 1967; 1976 (Box Series I-27)
  - Whittington, W. J., 1964-67 (Box Series I-27)
  - Whittle, Peter D. J., 1974 (Box Series I-27)
  - Wiedemann, [?] (Box Series I-28)
    See Ser.I, Clarke, Cyril A. (13 Dec. 1961)
  - Wiener, Alexander A., 1953-62 (Box Series I-28)
    The Lancet
  - Wigglesworth, Vincent B., 1966 (Box Series I-28)
  - John Wiley & Sons Ltd., 1967-76 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wilkinson, Walter, 1957-58 (Box Series I-28)
  - Williams, C. B., 1974-75 (Box Series I-28)
  - Williams, Duncan H., 1972 (Box Series I-28)
  - Williams, E. T., 1956 (Box Series I-28)
  - Williams, Jill M., 1971 (Box Series I-28)
  - Williams, K. R. (Mrs. ) (Box Series I-28)
  - Williams, W. G., 1968 (Box Series I-28)
  - Williams, Watkin, 1956-57 (Box Series I-28)
  - Williams, William, 1967-68 (Box Series I-28)
  - Williamson, Mark H., 1954-74 (Box Series I-28)
  - Willis, Judy, 1961 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wilson, Andrew, 1964 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wilson, Arthur C., 1972 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wilson, D. A., 1968 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wilson, E. J., 1961-63 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wilson, Harold, 1967 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wilson, J. F., 1972 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wilson, Kent H., 1958; 1965 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wilson, R. A., 1970 (Box Series I-28)
  - Winstanley, Carole, 1970 (Box Series I-28)
  - Winter, Aline S., 1953 (Box Series I-28)
    Brunet, [Peter C.]
  - Wireman, W., 1960 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wirtz, Erika A., 1964 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wolda, Henk, 1960; 1970 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wolff, Sheldon, 1972-73 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wood, C. C., 1970-72 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wood, Patricia, 1973 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wood, Roger J., 1970-76 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wood-Geesh, D., 1949 (Box Series I-28)
  - Woodhead, G. A., 1966 (Box Series I-28)
  - Woodrow, John C., 1971 (Box Series I-28)
  - Woodruff, David S., 1971 (Box Series I-28)
  - Wooldridge, Clara, 1960 (Box Series I-28)
  - Woolf, B., 1965 (Box Series I-28)
  - Woolham, Margaret, 1974 (Box Series I-28)
  - Workman, Peter, 1963-64 (Box Series I-28)
  - Worms, Charles (Box Series I-28)
  - Worth Publishers Inc., 1967-74 (Box Series I-28)